<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[CREATERATI]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[CREATERATI]]></description>
        <link>http://blog.eightcorners.co/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 00:39:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://blog.eightcorners.co/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 00:38:31 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Let's talk real business + some hard lessons I learned.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Let's talk real business + some hard lessons I learned.</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8fddfe5d-1638-4c63-9278-d68326018e0e.jpg" title="The biggest lesson really is something you probably already know: We need some daamm fine wine. Always. ;)
" alt="No occasion needed, because the wine makes the occasion.">,<p>Today, I thought I would write a few key lessons I’ve learned in business, not just design.<br>I want to not only share this with you but to also remind myself of these lessons years from now.</p>,<h2><strong>Lesson N°1</strong></h2>,<p>One of my favourite people in the world, <a href="https://makeitlookeasy.com.au/" title="The BOSS Course - Nat Tucker - The best personal style expert in Australia teaches how to be the boss of your wardrobe.">Nat Tucker from Make It Look Easy</a>, whom I’ve probably mentioned a few hundred times around here because she is just that amazing, has hired me to run Facebook Ads for her.<br>I don’t run a Facebook Ads agency, just to be clear, but I’ve always been fascinated with advertising, marketing and persuasion. <br>And because I could never say no to Nat, and to an opportunity to work with one of the most admirable entrepreneurs and human beings I’ve ever met? I said HELL YEAH.<br>Mind you, I’ve only ever ran ads for myself before. And an accountant friend. <br>On my first go, I spent $20. Crickets. My friend got leads but didn’t get sales. I decided: Facebook Ads don’t friggin’ work.<br>Desperate, I hired a marketing coach with all the money I earned from my last design project.<br>Surprise, surprise. He went on to teach me Facebook Ads.<br>The first week I ran ads again, I landed my very first design client via Facebook Ads. <br>She bought my $5999 design package. I spent $70.<br>The ad campaign also also helped connect me to you.<br>Talk about money well spent, plus time saved figuring out SEO, etc.<br>At that moment, my life changed. (So did my coach’s, who made a million dollars NET in 5 months with that one <a href="http://bit.ly/go-facebook-ads" title="How to Make $10k In Facebook Ads - Dan Henry">Facebook Ads course</a>).<br>Now that you have the back story, here is where it gets juicy:<br>I ran ads for my accountant friend and they converted at roughly 20%.<br>I’ve used ads to build my list and I get 45-50% conversion rates on my landing pages. (Conversion rates meaning 1 out of 2 people who clicked on my ad trusted me with their email address in exchange for a PDF that I thought would help them — you might have been one of them!)<br>When I got to that point I thought that was good. <br>But running ads for Nat? 65-70% conversion, baby. <br>I don’t think even the best marketing gurus out there convert as much.<br>Not only that, because she offered her <a href="http://bit.ly/therealhue" title="The Real Hue: What You Didn't Know About Colour">amazing ebook</a> after they signed up, NAT MADE MORE PROFIT THAN SHE SPENT RUNNING THE ADS.<br>Here’s a screenshot from a recent campaign we ran at 5X ROI:</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ea1c68a2-3fcb-4564-81e6-0c0d1340962b.png" title="Facebook Ads - Digital Product Screenshot at 5X ROI">,<p>This is on my third attempt, refined after the first few attempts. Even with the split-testing, course-corrections and apparent Facebook glitches this weekend?<br>We still made a profit. On autopilot.<br>While at the same time, reaching more women whose lives Nat would later change with her growing personal style empire.<br><strong>This is the epitome of a successful online business.</strong></p>,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/623e2a4d5dd3fa6b58b218ff59f635d7df352f04.png" title="Would you like a side of profit with all that awesome exposure?">,<p>The lesson?</p>,<h3>This is what’s possible when you have a great product, listen closely to what your customers want, and implement the right marketing strategy.</h3>,<p>(The ad strategy, I’m going to teach you very soon! The good, the bad, the ugly, and the mistakes I made that you can avoid!)<br>Which brings us to:</p>,<h2><strong>Lesson N°2</strong></h2>,<h3>Be there for your clients and customers, and never, ever forget who helped you get there.</h3>,<p>When you’re starting out in business without a mentor, it can sometimes feel like somebody pushed you in the water without first teaching you the basics of swimming. <br>You thrash around, freeze in indecision as you mull things over, and maybe by sheer luck or instinct, you find a way to doggy paddle enough to survive.<br>The hard truth? You can hire all the coaches and buy all the courses you need (some will work, some won't), but in the end, you will need to let go of the buoy and swim. <br>To try different strokes and see which one works for you.<br>Don’t rely on anyone sticking around to throw you a life jacket. (Though sometimes you’d be surprised to find that someone’s actually got your back.)<br><strong>While this is a fact of life, this does NOT in any way mean that we can’t do it differently.</strong><br>When you learn to swim, even do marathons, and you’re able to start teaching others (usually the ones who cheered you on from the sidelines, as they prepare to get in themselves), <strong>be there for them, always</strong>. <br>Just because you had to learn on your own doesn’t mean you have to leave others to do the same. <br>The world would be a much better place if we all made real connections. <br>And this is what Nat does beautifully. And this is coming back 3x more than the average successful business.<br>This is the excellence we should be aiming for. There's no settling for the “average”.</p>,<h2><strong>Lesson N°3</strong></h2>,<h3>To be successful online, you have to have a set of skills.</h3>,<p>(My <a href="http://bit.ly/go-facebook-ads" title="Dan Henry - Facebook Ads and Digital Marketing Expert">marketing coach Dan Henry</a> just mentioned this today as well, and he is totally right.)<br>Unless you have the budget to hire the best and most reputable companies?<br>You have to do it yourself.<br>There’s just no other way around it. <br>I learned design out of necessity, and luckily, I found that I had a knack and love for it. <br>I learned Facebook Ads and marketing because you need to be in the trenches to see what works and what doesn’t. <br>I had to learn how to sell, and not in the sleazy way. <br>Selling is actually the easiest thing.<br><strong>Once you have a great product, because you listened to your customers? <br>It will sell itself.</strong><br>For the longest time, I avoided writing copy and believed I sucked at it. <br>Until I relented and thought heck, I should at least learn the basics. <br>And now, Nat hired me for that too. <br>I help write copy for her Facebook Ads and her landing pages. <br>I would spot the gems in her beautiful Facebook Page posts &amp; emails, and put those in her ebooks. I just add some more structure and finishing touches.<br>As I write this, I’m getting teary-eyed because I am just so overjoyed that it is all making sense now. And I still cannot believe it works.<br>(I'm sure Nat could probably do better with a pro marketer/copywriter, but to see that my words and strategy are not failing and actually converting well? For someone else? That feels pretty darned good.)</p>,<h1>And I can’t wait to share everything I know with you.</h1>,<p>I'd love to share my expertise in design + tech, with a touch of copywriting &amp; advertising, so that together we can change the world.<br>It sounds like an absolute cliche, but I don’t care, because we all know this is what we are meant to do in this world.<br>To change the world in your own unique way that only you, and nobody else, can.<br>We all have unique gifts and with the right roadmaps and strategies, I can help you bring it out for all the world to see.<br>So when you’re ready, come join me on The Brand Tour. <br>Our first leg starts on 1st March 2017. And there’s still crazy priced early bird seats waiting for you if you <a href="http://gretcho.link/ecourses" title="The Brand Tour - DIY Design Masterclass - Mentorship Program - Online Course">grab it quickly</a>. <br>Just as a hint: the early bird seats start at $98, and this is for a mentorship program not a course. Told you, I'm pretty crazy. ;)<br>The catch? There's only one ticket each, incrementing to $598 on towards the early bird price, which will only be available until 28th February. After that, it's $898.<br>Why? Because I'm rewarding you for trusting me before the tour/ class starts.<br>So get in early at a price you'll never see again. <br>Just head on over here to get your seat now: <a href="http://eightcorners.us13.list-manage1.com/track/click?u=7cd0ee9b8caa450bbc55bfd2b&amp;id=d75a89edb6&amp;e=2d0cdeeb8f">http://gretcho.link/ecourses</a><br>Before I send this to the ad gods, who seem to be smiling down at me right this moment. ;)<br>Got any questions? Want something covered that I haven't listed?<br>Head on over to our <a href="http://eightcorners.us13.list-manage.com/track/click?u=7cd0ee9b8caa450bbc55bfd2b&amp;id=ad8c34617c&amp;e=2d0cdeeb8f">Design Lounge</a> or reply to this email and let me know your thoughts!</p>,<a href="http://gretcho.link/ecourses" data-role="cta">Grab your early bird ticket here</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.eightcorners.co/and-i-cant-wait-to-share-everything-i-know-with-you/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">26c092c2-0270-466b-bf7e-2962c08a394b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 23:29:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Free Gradients Collection by itmeo.com]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Free Gradients Collection by itmeo.com</h1><p>Come to WebGradients.com for 180 beautiful linear gradients in CSS3, Photoshop and Sketch. This collection is curated by top designers and totally free.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://webgradients.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bfefd247-5a1b-4307-a628-73ae01de0afc</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 12:58:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colour Personality: Could Fresh Green be your match?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/b37adc264f346ea36e734f481403ddca/croprotate.png?cropheight=807&cropwidth=1200&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Fe3ab5e30-18ce-4a41-a376-f5e9d759afee.png&x=0&y=197">,<h1>Colour Personality: Could Fresh Green be your match?</h1>,<p>Doing anything Valentine's Day?</p>,<p>Whether or not you celebrate it, let's have fun with it! ;)</p>,<p>Introducing...Colour Matchmaking series.</p>,<p>This is a little experiment on doing a little spin on the whole colour psychology thing...we're going to give them life!</p>,<p>In the form of a personal dating ad.</p>,<p>Crazy? Weird? Guilty as charged.</p>,<p>But as David Ogilvy once said:</p>,<blockquote>The best ideas come as jokes. Make your thinking as funny as possible.</blockquote>,<p>So let's get on with it! Ready?<br>Imagine the following as a personal ad in a newspaper, old-school style:</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.eightcorners.co/colour-personality-could-fresh-green-be-your-match/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">de3a27a3-cd18-41c2-9a0c-5bc06c01705d</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 01:45:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Are you using the right colours for your brand?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/90a0f7f5-6d52-46c1-9a5a-e1637e886589.jpg">,<h1>Are you using the right colours for your brand?</h1>,<p>I spent most of the weekend just taking in lots of inspiration (I find that headspace and lots of eye candy&nbsp;helps the creative mind, and no it's not just caffeine&nbsp;&nbsp;) and I can't wait to share them with you!<br>From the wonderful Lunar New Year celebrations here in Melbourne to the unreal yet uber-inspiring Australian Open tennis final with Federer and Nadal. (Two of the top tennis champs&nbsp;in our lifetime!)<br>I just loved how generous, gracious, and tenacious both legends are.&nbsp;<br>Most of all, how Federer and Nadal leveraged their own strengths, which they used to conquer the other’s weaknesses.<br>Nadal used power and spin on his shots, targeting Federer’s weak backhand, and how Federer used wit and persistence to target Nadal’s backhand issues as well.<br>Which made me think a lot about branding and visual identity.<br>We all have something in us and in our businesses that separate us from others.&nbsp;<br>Nadal had power, Federer had tactics. What's yours?<br>Can't think of any? No worries!<br></p>,<h2>3 quick questions to help you refine your branding</h2>,<p>1. What makes you angry and annoyed in your industry? What is it about your industry you’d like to change?&nbsp;<br>2. What are your weaknesses? Can you somehow turn them into strengths?<br>3. How can you tie both in to your brand’s visual identity?<br>As for me, I don’t like how design and creativity is perceived by many as a talent or gift for the select few.<br>How it sometimes can feel elitist, unattainable, impossible.&nbsp;<br>My weaknesses? I’m an unknown, self-taught designer with no prestigious awards or degrees from a leading university. I’m not even a veteran yet in any sense of the word. &nbsp;<br>I’m also an introvert so thinking about PR and video gives me the hives.&nbsp;<br>But I’ve found ways to get around this by keeping things simple, to get creative every day, and to continually strive for excellence.<br></p>,<h2>Simplicity, creativity and excellence.&nbsp;</h2>,<p>That’s why my brand just consists of black (sometimes near-black navy) and white for simplicity, &nbsp;pale gold and silver for excellence, and bright purple to add a hint of creativity and playfulness.&nbsp;<br>Your turn! Let me know what yours are, I'd love to know.<br>Still stuck picking colours? Got great news for you!<br>Over the next few weeks, I’ll be introducing colours to you in a bit of an unconventional way.&nbsp;<br>Sure, there’s colour psychology charts out there (just check out Pinterest) that kinda give you an idea, but my problem with them is that they are too general.&nbsp;<br>For instance, they say blue is for trust, efficiency, intelligence. But there’s so many shades of blue — did you pick the right shade?&nbsp;<br>What about the right combo?<br>(Oh, and in case you’re wondering, my favourite reference for stunning colour combinations? Check it out: The Real Hue: What You Didn’t Know About Colour.)<br>Excited? I know I am. ;)<br>Is there a specific colour you want to get to know first?<br>Head on over to our&nbsp;<a href="http://eightcorners.us13.list-manage.com/track/click?u=7cd0ee9b8caa450bbc55bfd2b&amp;id=1f1e50eca3&amp;e=2d0cdeeb8f">Design Lounge</a>&nbsp;or reply to this email and we'll move it higher up the queue!&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.eightcorners.co/are-you-using-the-right-colours-for-your-brand/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b3dc3271-131f-4828-9a21-dff29ac5eeac</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 03:13:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Your hair is a mess.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Your hair is a mess.</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d740ba2f-0f32-485e-ac94-4a8161b9614f.jpg">,<p>Ever had someone say this to you? Or of you?</p>,<p>And, by any chance, did you find yourself wanting to defend yourself?</p>,<p>Would it really help to tell them that you’ve just been travelling for over 12 hours?</p>,<p>And that you haven’t brought your trusty hair conditioner?</p>,<p>Or had time to blow-dry your hair? </p>,<p>Which you never had to do anyway because you live in a non-humid climate and it’s punishing you for taking it to a humid one?</p>,<p>Or that you just had it cut 12 inches short, with layers, so you can get a “messy” look?</p>,<p>Then you turn to the one person whose opinion matters to you.</p>,<p>“Do you think my hair is a mess?”, you ask. </p>,<p>Because years of preconditioned belief that you’re unpretty is hard to shake off.</p>,<p>He answers, “What are you talking about? I don’t think your hair looks messy. You always look good to me.”</p>,<p>At that point, you realise that there’s the one of the two opinions that really matters to you. </p>,<p>And it ain’t theirs.</p>,<p>I happen to like my messy hair.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.eightcorners.co/your-hair-is-a-mess/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">98eb9f3f-99bf-45ca-8af1-842d8e0fd3ea</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 03:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[8 Canva Alternatives You Didn’t Know About]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>8 Canva Alternatives You Didn’t Know About</h1>,<h3>…because we all know Canva is a peach.</h3>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a8647d55-2116-433d-8498-43b81e331f88.png" title="8 Canva Alternatives You Should Know About" alt="Infographic on 8 Canva Alternatives">,<p>One of my fave quotes?</p>,<blockquote>&quot;You can be the ripest, juiciest peach in the world, and there&apos;s still going to be somebody who hates peaches.&quot;
&horbar; Dita Von Teese</blockquote>,<p>I’m gonna say this right now: I don’t like peaches.</p>,<p>And to me, Canva is a peach.</p>,<p>So if you’re like me who thinks Canva is a peach (sorry, I’m loving this too much, aren’t I?), here are a few Canva alternatives for you!</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.eightcorners.co/8-canva-alternatives-you-should-know-about/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ca775e2f-9a10-42aa-af6a-b6d1e1cb5810</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 04:36:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On the importance of Negative Space…in design and life.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ec8e2f69-e722-497c-897c-acf8e49d8a25.jpg">,<h1>On the importance of Negative Space…in design and life.</h1>,<p>“ <strong>in a world filled with chaos and clutter, clean design stands out</strong>.”</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.eightcorners.co/on-the-importance-of-negative-spacein-design-and-life/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">68568718-cf12-4070-bed2-437eed1f1f00</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 04:18:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How I Design With Negative Space]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>How I Design With Negative Space</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8b2e9ff6-1b40-44f8-89e8-e32062039fa5.png" title="Guido&apos;s Window" alt="Second in this #createdaily #designdaily series is a sketch of Guido&apos;s window.">]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.eightcorners.co/how-i-design-with-negative-space/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">87d4041c-f5ae-4a05-950c-18091ed9acd7</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 04:53:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tutorial: How to Change The Title Font in Google Slides]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/00431939-07ad-43d7-8002-901bcfd3f194.gif" title="Tutorial: How to Change The Title Font in Google Slides" alt="DIY Design It Yourself - Create Your Own eBook Template, PDF Template">,<h1>Tutorial: How to Change The Title Font in Google Slides</h1>,<a href="https://www.etsy.com/au/shop/eightcornerscreative" data-role="cta">Buy Pre-Made Templates Here</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.eightcorners.co/tutorial-how-to-change-the-title-font-in-google-slides/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3bedc287-6e5b-488b-90c4-ac3588c40c7e</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 05:30:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[There are only two emotions: love and fear.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/2fabf300-d35d-42ba-9373-0d86e297cf52.png" title="The Two Emotions" alt="Abstract Art using Autodesk SketchBook">,<h1>There are only two emotions: love and fear.</h1>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.eightcorners.co/there-are-only-two-emotions-love-and-fear/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3794b065-7f29-4127-bdd3-f9ed55fd23f2</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 00:30:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>